Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Documentation of Executions, 1730-2008; Undated; 2; 44.5 cubic ft.
  - State, 1730-2008; Undated; 2.1
    - Indiana, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1881-1984; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Iowa, B, 1935-1974; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Iowa, C-J, 1889-1975; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Iowa, J-P, 1865-1983; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Iowa, R-W, 1901-1979; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Iowa, executions recorded in county and state records, 1850-1977; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Kansas, A-H, 1867-1989 (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Kansas, H-L, 1943-1962; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Kansas, L-T, 1887-1989; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Kansas, executions recorded in statewide records, 1950; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Kentucky, A-B, 1857-1990; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Kentucky, B, 1899-1990; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Kentucky, B, 1911-1990; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Kentucky, C, 1885-1990; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Kentucky, C-D, 1885-1997; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Kentucky, E-G, 1886-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Kentucky, G, 1849-1986; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Kentucky, H, 1823-1996; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Kentucky, H-J, 1858-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Kentucky, J-M, 1887-1994; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Kentucky, M, 1829-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Kentucky, M-P, 1878-1992; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Kentucky, Q-S, 1853-1974; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Kentucky, S-T, 1868-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Kentucky, T, 1883-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Kentucky, U-W, 1879-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Kentucky, W-Y, 1899-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Kentucky, multiple executions, 1941-1975; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Kentucky, multiple executions, 1892-1990; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Kentucky, executions recorded in county histories, 1883-1983; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Kentucky, executions recorded in county histories, 1886-1972; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Kentucky, executions recorded in statewide records, 1974-1987; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Kentucky, unconfirmed executions, 1850; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Louisiana, A-B, 1885-1984; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Louisiana, B, 1897-1993; Undated (Box 17 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Louisiana, B, 1831-1997; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Louisiana, B-C, 1837-1995; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Louisiana, C, 1879-1987; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Louisiana, C-D, 1867-1989; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Louisiana, D-E, 1831-1979; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Louisiana, F-G, 1879-1988; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Louisiana, G, 1878-1987; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Louisiana, H-J, 1818-1996; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Louisiana, J, 1930-1991; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Louisiana, K-L, 1830-1988; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Louisiana, M, 1806-1991; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Louisiana, M-P, 1893-1987; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Louisiana, P-R, 1906-1990; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Louisiana, S, 1905-1993; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Louisiana, S-W, 1837-1995; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Louisiana, W, 1885-1998; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Louisiana, W-Y, 1885-1963; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Louisiana, unidentified executions, 1812-1984; Undated (Box 18 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Louisiana, multiple executions, 1896-1966; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Louisiana, multiple executions, 1837-1984; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Louisiana, executions recorded in city and parish histories, 1885-1990 (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Louisiana, executions recorded in statewide records, 1936-1989; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Louisiana, executions recorded in statewide records, 1923-1986; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Louisiana, unconfirmed executions, 1815-1908; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Maine, 1788-1988; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Maryland, A-C, 1820-1991; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Maryland, D-G, 1792-1998; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Maryland, H-L, 1808-1991; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Maryland, M-T, 1845-1994; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Maryland, V-W, 1844-1991; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Maryland, unidentified executions, multiple executions, and executions recorded in statewide records, 1858-1989; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts, A-B, 1834-1988; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts, B-C, 1796-1988 (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts, C-D, 1739-1984; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Massachusetts, D, 1879-1982; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts, E-F, 1730-1989; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts, G, 1849-1989; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts, G-H, 1849-1989; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts, I-K, 1830-1977; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts, K-O, 1857-1988; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 22)
    - Massachusetts, O-R, 1850-1983; Undated (Box 19 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 23)
    - Massachusetts, R-S, 1771-1997; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts, S, 1936-1991; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts, S, 1935-1991; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts, T, 1812-1997; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts, T-Z, 1806-1988; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts, multiple executions, 1820-1990; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1878-1992; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts, executions recorded in statewide records, 1849-1988; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts, executions recorded in statewide records, 1971-1992; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Michigan, 1924-1986; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Minnesota, B-H, 1889-1991; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Minnesota, H-Y, 1897-1992; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Minnesota, multiple executions, 1962; 1976; 1987 (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Mississippi, A-B, 1837-1976; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Mississippi, B-C, 1824-1978; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Mississippi, C-E, 1818-1989; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Mississippi, F-G, 1849-1990; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Mississippi, G-H, 1846-1992; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Mississippi, H-J, 1845-1946; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Mississippi, J-L, 1857-1987; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Mississippi, L-M, 1852-1947; Undated (Box 20 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Mississippi, M-P, 1845-1986; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Mississippi, P-R, 1841-1977; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Mississippi, S, 1877-1986; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Mississippi, S-T, 1849-1995; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Mississippi, U-W, 1851-1948; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Mississippi, W-Y, 1873-1988; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Mississippi, unconfirmed executions, 1828-1950 (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Mississippi, unidentified and multiple executions, 1851-1948; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Mississippi, executions recorded in county histories, 1884-1981; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Mississippi, executions recorded in statewide records, 1875-1992; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Missouri, A-B, 1849-1953; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Missouri, B, 1863-1993; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Missouri, B-C, 1874-1991; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Missouri, C-E, 1821-1991; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Missouri, E-G, 1850-1995; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Missouri, G, 1879-1995; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Missouri, H-J, 1883-1992; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Missouri, J-K, 1886-2001; Undated (Box 21 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Missouri, K-L, 1831-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Missouri, L-M, 1846-1993 (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Missouri, M, 1931-1997 (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Missouri, M-O, 1854-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Missouri, O-P, 1877-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Missouri, P-R, 1857-1999; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Missouri, S, 1824-1997; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Missouri, S-T, 1830-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Missouri, T-W, 1879-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Missouri, W-Z, 1888-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Missouri, unidentified and multiple executions, 1841-1991; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Missouri, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1883-1990; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Missouri, executions recorded in county histories, 1883-1981; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Missouri, executions recorded in county histories, 1881-1985; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Missouri, executions recorded in statewide records, 1881; 1949; 1987; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Missouri, unconfirmed executions, 1837-1913 (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Montana, A-H, 1882-1996; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Montana, K-M, 1879-1998; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Montana, M-R, 1878-1952; Undated (Box 22 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Montana, S-Z, 1888-1975; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Montana, multiple executions and executions recorded in statewide records, 1975; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Nebraska, B-F, 1891-1943; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Nebraska, H-J, 1887-1996; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Nebraska, M-N, 1890-1986 (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Nebraska, N-P, R, 1903-1994 (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Nebraska, R-S, 1879-1994; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Nebraska, S-T, W, 1917-1976; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Nebraska, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1892; 1937; 1994; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Nevada, A-B, 1948-1990; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Nevada, C-F, 1949-1989; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Nevada, G-K, 1882-1994; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Nevada, L-M, 1868-1985; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Nevada, M, P, R, S, 1874-1999; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Nevada, S-T, V-W, 1874-1989 (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Nevada, multiple executions and executions recorded in statewide records, 1922-1958; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - New Hampshire, A-H, 1849-1991; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New Hampshire, K-T, 1845-1997; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - New Hampshire, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1884-1973; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - New Jersey, A-B, 1860-1946; Undated (Box 23 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - New Jersey, B, 1895-1988; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - New Jersey, C, 1883-1999; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - New Jersey, C, 1879-1976; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - New Jersey, D, 1857-1985; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - New Jersey, D-F, 1883-1990 (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - New Jersey, F, 1856-1985; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - New Jersey, G-H, 1796-1949; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - New Jersey, H (Hauptmann), 1932-1995 (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - New Jersey, H (Hauptmann), 1931-1991 (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - New Jersey, H (Hauptmann), 1935-1991; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - New Jersey, H, 1837-1978; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - New Jersey, H-J, 1875-1958; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - New Jersey, K-M, 1859-1994; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - New Jersey, M, 1881-1987; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - New Jersey, N-S, 1867-1992; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - New Jersey, S-Z, 1867-1994; Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - New Jersey, unconfirmed executions, Undated (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New Jersey, multiple executions, 1915-1943 (Box 24 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - New Jersey, executions recorded in county, regional, and statewide records, 1881-1987; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - New Mexico, A-H, 1861-1986; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - New Mexico, H-M, 1885-1985; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - New Mexico, M-W, 1883-1992; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - New Mexico, Y, 1946-1985 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - New Mexico, unidentified and multiple executions, 1897-1991; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - New Mexico, executions recorded in city, county, and statewide records, 1901-1982; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - New Mexico, unconfirmed executions, 1948 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - New York, A, 1882-1979 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - New York, A, 1821-1967; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - New York, A-B, 1880-1964; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - New York, B, 1837-1994 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - New York, B, 1876-1991; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - New York, B, 1935-1990 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - New York, B, 1932-1975; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - New York, B, 1878-1994; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - New York, B-C, 1869-1977; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New York, C, 1829-1951 (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - New York, C, 1897-1988; Undated (Box 25 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - New York, C, 1880-1991; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - New York, C-D, 1854-1991 (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - New York, D, 1878-1951; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - New York, D, 1813-1977; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - New York, D-E, 1871-1990; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - New York, E, 1876-1975; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - New York, E-F, 1825-1986; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - New York, F, 1910-1991; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - New York, F-G, 1866-1979; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - New York, G, 1935-1951; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - New York, G, 1865-1981; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - New York, G, 1876-1971; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - New York, G, 1881-1989 (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - New York, G-H, 1876-1989; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - New York, H, 1819-1989; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - New York, H, 1817-1978; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - New York, H-J, 1888-1975; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New York, J-K, 1828-1988; Undated (Box 26 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - New York, K, 1865-1955; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - New York, K-L, 1834-1997; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - New York, L, 1874-1991; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - New York, L-M, 1883-1984; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - New York, M, 1854-1988; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - New York, M, 1876-1985; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - New York, M-N, 1937-1964; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - New York, O-P, 1866-1964; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - New York, P, 1880-1966; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - New York, R, 1933-1987; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - New York, R, 1881-1964; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - New York, R, 1858-1964; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - New York, R-S, 1851-1975; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - New York, S, 1923-1984; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - New York, S, 1879-1987; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - New York, S, 1927-1991; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - New York, S-T, 1878-1991; Undated (Box 27 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New York, T-V, 1888-1984; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - New York, V-W, 1917-1963; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - New York, W, 1819-1988; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - New York, W, 1858-1984; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - New York, W-Z, 1797-1989; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - New York, unidentified, 1988 (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - New York, slave insurrections, 1928-1988; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - New York, multiple executions, 1934-1964; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - New York, multiple executions, 1914-1988; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - New York, multiple executions, 1929-1975; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - New York, multiple executions, 1928-1955; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - New York, multiple executions, 1934-1985; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - New York, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1851-1963; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - New York, executions recorded in statewide records, 1857-1988; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - New York, executions recorded in statewide records, 1881-1974; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - New York, executions recorded in statewide records, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)